I saw let us dive into the program which I have P A third I will be giving this program
in a resource section as well as I will be giving the command how to compile this program
ok.
And you can convert it to exeef let me start explaining the program and here you can find
we have use several APA functions, Windows Start, H, I and Protebo Stream and Strings it is
like a library functions and next we have did a bool set privilege we have used a APA
function set privilege.
So, basically this function enables a specific privilege for the current process ok.
So, anyway we are going to execute this program in CMD.exe ok.
So, it enable the specified which privilege it needs to steal a token ok.
And it will be it will be enabling the SCD bug name the privilege that one ok.
So, this three lines is used to enable the privilege for a current process.
So, what privilege we need to access the token ok to steal the token.
So, this all the program is due to retrieve the value area of the privilege we need to
check that.
So, which privilege we have are so are we able to steal the token or not ok that is basically
and so it is the function to open up specified the process token.
So, let us dive on to the yeah basically this complete line will be setting the privilege
for a current process.
So, what are the things we need to what are the things we need to set to privilege set
to do a access token manipulation of that ok.
So, the next one we have this is the important function let us remember this ok.
We have a handle we are doing a handle to get a token ok it is a function to get access
token from a target process ok anyway we are going to steal a token from another process
ok.
So, this functionality are doing that it will be stealing the token from a from the another
process ok.
So, basically we have used this get token with the open process of process query limited
information ok.
So, this is a very important line we are going to detect this token manipulation attack
in the next video you can see the similar function ok the similar parameter in the next
video also we have used several things like token handle we are going to handle that token
and we are going to use that right in the elevator process.
So, the next line we are going to create a new process with the store and token ok.
So, basically this is the entire command and it will be opening the it will be elevating
the process CMD.txt.
So, you can do any sort of executable if you have a malware.txt you can do a malware here
ok.
So, the entire program is very simple we are going to set all the enable all the privilege
for a current process to steal the access token from the remote process from the target
process.
The next one we are doing a handle to get the access token from the target process which
process we are going to steal and finally we are using the stored token and we are creating
a new CMD.txt from that ok.
So, let me open my VM and I have already compiled this program it will be sitting in a
directory. So, I am going to use the token stealer 1, so here I can see a same program.
So, I will be giving the command how to compile this CPP file.
So, you can use the x64 or x64 native tool the visual studio based tools to compile this
CPP file and you will be getting a exe from that.
So, let me open so I already said we need to run this program as an administrator mode
because we need to set some privilege right.
You can see the code we need to enable some privilege for that to enabling that privilege
you need to administer the level access control ok.
Let me open up power shell better, process, so I am going to steal the win log on token
ok.
So, it was running as a bit of 776 let me open my ok.
Let me redirect into the directory first and I will be using the token stealer 1.txt.
So, if I execute that it was asking for a bit which bid I need to from which bid I need
to steal the token.
So, I will be using the bid of win log on process 776 ok in between let me open a process
hacker ok my machine was shutting down let wait for a few time yeah let us receive that
my machine has been restarted.
So, my program will be open stealer and it was asking for a bit I am going to use the
bit of win log on process 772 in between let me open a process hacker to form my understanding
where is the win log on ok here you can find a win log on 772 let me execute this 772 and
now you can see it has found another process CMD.exe right so let me go to the process
hacker now you can see CMD so this CMD will be running as a win log on process privilege
ok the higher privilege so basically this is running as a very higher privilege ok.
So, the token has been not listed or anything be read enough but if I execute so here
you can see a command problem with a system mandatory level but if you see here so where
I execute or the program so this only have a high mandatory level of privilege but this
has a system mandatory level so we have successfully performed a access token manipulation
attack so this is how you need to execute that ok so I have all the privileges to do anything
in a Windows ok so that is all about the video how in the next video we are going to
see how we can detect this attack ok so let us stop off and we will see you in the next
video guys thank you.